	
	INTRODUCTION

	This game was created as a project for my Digital Art and Design class also known as DAAD. When I finished the project I decided to make it as impressive as possible. So now with this game I am constantly working on it making changes all the time to it. Even though its on a command line it is still neat to make things like this, as it gives you the feeling that you are playing an old text based gameon Dos or Unix, where it was all command line, well most of the time, to be more specific, a time where the modern GUI did not exist, and you had no use for a mouse. The goal of the project was to make a rock,paper, scissors game in Python, but like I said at the beginning it became more than a class project for me, it became a big project in which I wanted to create an old school text based game. And this one thing has led to inspiration to create more things like this. Its a different type of experience to create something like this that looks hard to make but in reality is simple and fun to create rather than make something that is modern, and looks simple, but is extremely complex when it comes to coding.

!!!!IMPORTANT!!!!
	Sometimes the computer seems to get stuck and keeps picking the same weapon constantly. Its not a bug and the game is fully functional. It may be caused because it has only three variables to pick from.


<Version History>
/////////////////////////////////
|2/12/2014 -V1.0 Intital release
/////////////////////////////////
|           5448 Total characters
/////////////////////////////////	 
|            227 Lines of code
/////////////////////////////////

<Planned updates>
-Total re-build in progess to simplify code and reduce the amount of code.

-Next update will include a copy of the current game file with detailed documentation.

